import { Exercise } from ".";

export const JOBS: Exercise[] = [
  {
    "question": "врач",
    "answer": "wracz",
    "extra": "👨‍⚕️"
  },
  {
    "question": "учитель",
    "answer": "uczitiel",
    "extra": "👨‍🏫"
  },
  {
    "question": "повар",
    "answer": "powar",
    "extra": "👨‍🍳"
  },
  {
    "question": "инженер",
    "answer": "inżenier",
    "extra": "👨‍💻"
  },
  {
    "question": "художник",
    "answer": "chudożnik",
    "extra": "👨‍🎨"
  },
  {
    "question": "пилот",
    "answer": "pilot",
    "extra": "👨‍✈️"
  },
  {
    "question": "строитель",
    "answer": "stroitiel",
    "extra": "👷"
  },
  {
    "question": "писатель",
    "answer": "pisatiel",
    "extra": "✍️"
  },
  {
    "question": "музыкант",
    "answer": "muzykant",
    "extra": "🎵"
  },
  {
    "question": "фотограф",
    "answer": "fotograf",
    "extra": "📸"
  }
];
